presearch.org 2011-12-13

# Vizibility.com - Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy

Welcome to Vizibility.com (the "Site"), a patent pending service operated by Vizibility Inc. Vizibility provides PreSearch services (our "Services") that make it easy for You to create, share and monitor personalized PreSearches for one or more search engines via our proprietary platform (the "Vizibility Platform"). The terms "Vizibility", "us", "we" or "our" refers to Vizibility Inc., the owner of the Site and Services. The term "You" or "Your" refers to the person accessing or using the Site and Services, or the company or organization on whose behalf that person accesses the Site and Services. 

We have created this policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of information about You. This privacy policy applies to information that You provide to us when you use our Services or the Vizibility Platform. 

Below we provide you with our Privacy Policy, where we intend to be transparent about any information we collect, how we intend to use the information, and what choices you have when you register with us and use our website or Services.

### Our Privacy Policy in short:

  * Your privacy remains under your control
  * We will only use personal information you provide us according to the terms of this Privacy policy
  * In order to use certain features of our platform, you will provide a limited amount of personal information
  * Unless required for delivery of the Services, we will never disclose your personally-identifiable information to any third party without your consent or unless we are required to so by law
  * You can cancel your Vizibility account at any time

### What information do we collect?

During use of the Services and the Vizibility Platform, we collect various types of data, usage statistics, demographic and preference information and other personal information as described below.

When registering on our website or using certain features of Vizibility, we may collect personally identifiable information about you that may include, but is not limited to your username, email address and employment history (the "Personally Identifiable Information").

In order to use the Services, we require that you provide certain Personally Identifiable Information. We may also request additional Personally Identifiable Information from time to time thereafter. Providing such additional Personally Identifiable Information is entirely optional, although some of our Services may not function without such information.

We use your Personally Identifiable Information mainly to provide the Services to you, as applicable, to track and provide analytics, and to administer your inquiries. We may also use your Personally Identifiable Information to contact you with email, newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

Additionally, we capture, store and transmit your IP address to Google and/or any other search engine requiring it, for the sole purpose of enabling the search engine to verify that the search request is valid. Once your IP address has been transmitted to Google and/or any other supported search engine, its specific use by these search engines will be governed by their own terms of service and/or privacy policies.

### Vizibility SearchMe™ Button and Link Users

If you are simply using or accessing the Site or the Services by clicking on a Vizibility SearchMe button or link, we collect certain information which cannot be used to personally identify you, and which may be provided to third parties. Such non-personal data ordinarily includes non-identifiable aggregate, summary, usage data, location data, and other behavioral data and may include, by way of example, statistics regarding total users, information regarding types of Internet browsers used by users, and behavioral usage patterns. We also collect non-personal data about each user's IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our website and Services.

### Log Data

"Log Data" means information sent by your browser including, but not limited to your computer's IP address, referring HTTP address, current HTTP address, time of the access and other statistics. 

We also collect Log Data each time you visit third party websites that use our Services. We analyze Log Data from different websites and combine it with other non-Personally Identifiable Information to produce reports and data that are made available to Vizibility customers appropriate for their products or services. We do not link Log Data to any other Personally Identifiable Information about you or otherwise attempt to discover your identity. 

### Minors

If providing personal data, you certify that you are over the age of 13. As such, we do not collect or maintain personal data from individuals we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of the Site or the Services are designed to attract people under 13. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. Thus, if we ever obtain knowledge that that a user is under 13, we will take steps to remove that customer's personal data from our databases and to prevent the user from utilizing the Site and Services.

### Cookies

Like many websites and platforms, we use cookies on our website and Services (by placing or reading them via your browser) to save your registration information for future logins. We also utilize cookies to enable certain features of the Site and Services to better understand how you interact with the Services and to monitor usage and web traffic routing on our website and Services. We also use cookies when you visit the Site and Services to collect Log Data, as described in the Log Data section above. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting browser cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Services.

### How do we use and disclose collected information?

We do not share Personally Identifiable Information collected on the Site and Services, including email addresses, with third parties for their direct marketing or solicitation.

Log Data and Usage Information. We may use your information (a) to deliver the Services desired by you (including any customization features requested by you), (b) to improve our services to you, (c) to personalize content and offers that may be of interest to you, (d) to respond to your inquiries, and (e) to fulfill your request for products or services. We may use non-Personally Identifiable Information, like your IP address, to analyze statistical site usage and to customize the Site's content, layout and Services. We may share the following information with third parties, including, but not limited to, vendors that support the operation of the Site and Services: Log Data collected on both the Site and Services, as well as aggregated anonymous information resulting from the analysis of such Log Data for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to, usage patterns, behavioral patterns, and traffic and demographic analysis. 

Third Party Providers. We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the Services, to provide the Services on our behalf, to perform services related to administration of the Site and Services (including, without limitation, maintenance, hosting and database management services, and administration). These third parties have access to your Personally Identifiable Information and Log Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

Compliance with Law. Vizibility cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We disclose Personally Identifiable Information and Log Data to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Vizibility or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being illegal or legally actionable. 

Business Transfers. Vizibility may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personally Identifiable Information and Log Data, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

International Transfer. Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside Canada and choose to provide information to Vizibility, please be advised that we transfer Personally Identifiable Information to Canada and process it there. Your consent to this privacy policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

### Links to Other Sites

The Site and Services contain links to other third party websites and services. If you choose to click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party's website or service. The fact that we link to a website or service is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites or services. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from you. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

### Our Commitment to Data Security

Please be aware that, although we endeavor to provide reasonable security for information in our possession and control, no security system can prevent against all potential security breaches, and we bear no liability for uses or disclosures of personal data or non-personal data arising in connection with the theft thereof. Likewise, you are responsible for safeguarding the confidentiality of passwords to the Site and Services, and we bear no liability for access to, or use or disclosure of personal data if such access, use or disclosure arises in connection with the theft or disclosure (whether intentional or negligent) of such user's password.

### Changes To This Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the Site so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we will disclose it. Any such posted changes will be effective upon the date indicated by the posting. Your continued access to and/or use of the Site or our services constitutes your assent to, and acceptance of, this policy, including all posted changes for which we have provided notice.

Last Updated: September 2010
